Nobody Know What A Killer Looks Like
Slaughterhouse 2 is a horror film directed by Rick Roessler.
Unlike Buddy Bacon in the original 'Slaughterhouse' his brother Cleavon
left the blood-splattered pig farm for a better life.
But just like his father, Cleavon has a mute son who has a
passion for home-reared, flame-grilled Wonder Jerky.
Anyone who strays into Bacon's ranch, of abandoned Americana cars,
will soon become part of the Wonder Jerky success story.
Bucky Buchanan, played by Rick Roessler.
Sheriff Liz Birden, played by Sherry Leigh.
Mel Webber, played by Jim Lairmore.
Ashley Wilmington, played by Mary Grondona.
Emily, played by Madi Lewis.
Self, played by Dave Fogel.
Slaughterhouse-Five, or, The Children's Crusade: A Duty-Dance with Death is a 1969
semi-autobiographic science fiction-infused anti-war novel by Kurt Vonnegut.
It follows the life experiences of Billy Pilgrim, from his early years, to his time as an
American soldier and chaplain's assistant during World War II, to the post-war years.
Throughout the novel, Billy frequently travels back and forth through time.
The protagonist deals with a temporal crisis as a result
of his post-war psychological trauma.
The text centers on Billy's capture by the German Army and his survival of the Allied firebombing of
Dresden as a prisoner of war, an experience that Vonnegut endured as an American serviceman.
The work has been called an example of "unmatched moral clarity" and
"one of the most enduring anti-war novels of all time".
The tone is dark.